Guide to the Lewis Lloyd Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 1995 Acquisition, 1880-1984; Series I; 45.46; (53 boxes) + 33 broadsides, 11 art
  - Oversize posters and art work
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company. Goscinny Wystep Baletu Amerykanskiego, poster in Polish. (#66), 1964 (Box 75 (Broadside))
    - Contemporary Voices. Merce Cunningham, Robert Creeley, Stan Vanderbeek, Billy Klaver, John Cage, Len Lye, and Jack Tworkov. V.p.: [no year] January 23-February 17, poster. (Box 76 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham & Dance Company. Pohostinske Vystoupeni Moderniho Americkeho Baletu. Ostrava. Poster in Czech (#73), undated (Box 77 (Broadside))
    - Be-In-Again Film Festival. Easter Be-In films and sounds from Central Park, poster., 1967 May 12-14 (Box 78 (Broadside))
    - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, Holland Festival, [no year] June 29, [pre 1969], poster., [pre 1969] June 29 (Box 79 (Broadside))
    - Arkopolis, Jerzy Grotowski, Teatr- Laboratorium, poster in Polish. (#48), 1969 (Box 80 (Broadside))
    - Apocalypsis Figuris, Jerzy Grotowski, Teatr-Laboratorium, poster. (#47), 1968 (Box 81 (Broadside oversize))
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company w/John Cage, Stadsschouwburg - Amsterdam, poster, undated (Box 82 (Broadside oversize))
    - Leroi Jones, Slaveship, Theatre de la Cité, poster. (#51), 1970? (Box 83 (Broadside oversize))
    - Merce Cunningham & Dance Company, Latin American Tour, poster. (#79), 1968 (Box 84 (Broadside oversize))
    - View of East Haddam, Connecticut and Goodspeeds Landing (#10), 1880 (Box 85 (Art))
    - The Life and Times of Sigmund Freud, Brooklyn Academy of Music, Opera House, illustration after engraving by William Blake, R. Wilson. 23/300. (#98), 1969 December 18-20 (Box 86 (Art))
    - The Life and Times of Sigmund Freud, Brooklyn Academy of Music, Opera House, illustration after engraving by William Blake, R. Wilson. 23/300. (#98), 1969 December 18-20 (Box 87 (Art))
    - Laura Dean Dancers and Musicians, poster with art and signature of Michael Graves. (#50), 1982 (Box 88 (Art))
    - Coast Zone VII, Merce Cunningham, napkin (#63), undated (Box 89 (Art))
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, with John Cage, inscribed to Lewis Lloyd from "Merce" and "John," poster. (#81), 1977 (Box 90 (Art))
    - Svenska Baletten. Stockholm-Paris 1920-1925. Moderna Museet, Stockholm. (#126), 1969 (Box 91 (Art))
    - Abadallah, Det Kongelige Teater, August Bournonville, poster. (#30), undated (Box 92 (Art))
    - Ballet Praha. Divadelniho Studia. (#1), undated (Box 93 (Art))
    - Igor Stravinsky, Metropolitan Opera, 1981/1982, poster. (#43) (Box 94 (Art))
    - Théâtre de France, Merce Cunningham and Dance Company and Paul Taylor Dance Company. (#77; #94), 1966 (Box 95 (Art))
  - Audiovisual Material (Box 96)
    Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    (11 audiotape reels and four 8mm film reels)
    - Recordings of The Sap of Life and recordings of interviews, 1961 June; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888194)
    - Recording of the 1963 concert at Town Hall of the music of Earl Brown and Morton Feldman, 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888202)
    - Curtaintime News & Music of Broadway, WKCR-FM, undated; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888210)
    - The Sap of Life, undated; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888228)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888236)
    - WNTA, Air Check, 1961 October 10; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888244)
    - The Fantasticks production at the Charles Playhouse, Boston, 1961; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888251)
    - The Sap of Life first tape, undated; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888269)
    - Town Hall III, Earle Brown, "December 1952", "Pentathis", 1963 October 11; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888277)
    - Town Hall I, Feldman, "Vertical Thoughts" (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888285)
      Annotation describes tape running out and missing last four chords.
    - Town Hall II, Feldman, "The Straits of Magellan"..., 1963 October; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888293)
    - Four 8 mm reels (Box 96)
- October 1995 Acquisition, 1977-1994; Series II; 4; (4 boxes)
  This acquisition includes correspondence, notes, financial records, photographs, audiovisual material, printed material and ephemera. Includes files relating to the Sans Souci Theatre, The Twin Theatres Inc., Merce Cunningham Dance Company and the Twyla Tharp Dance Company.
  Box 103 contains audiovisual material. Restricted access. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Files and printed material related to education, funding, and development of the arts, 1982-1989; 18 (Box 97)
  - The CIVIL warS printed material, 1985 (Box 97)
    Related Materials
    There is an audiocassette related to this material that can be found in Box 96.
  - David Byrne: Music for The CIVIL warS for Knee Plays 1-13 (audiocassette), 1985; 1 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002104888301)
    This audiocasette is related to three folders of material titled "The CIVIL warS" printed material in Box 97.
  - WGBH, 1980; 2 (Box 97)
  - Twyla Tharp Dance Company, 1981-1992; 21 (Box 98)
  - "Twyla Tharp: Scrapbook" for ABS/ARTS Cable, 1982; YCALMSS752_0001; 1; 00:59:29 (Box 103, Item barcode 39002102339356)
    Restricted fragile material.
  - "Twyla Tharp: Confessions of a Corner Maker" - for CBS Cable, undated; YCALMSS752_0002; 1; 00:47:46 (Box 103, Item barcode 39002102339364)
  - Cunningham Dance Foundation, 1976-1987; 15 (Box 99)
  - Massachusetts Council on Arts and Humanities, 1977; 4 (Box 99)
  - Printed material, photographs, and correspondence related to various dancers and dance companies, 1980-1984; 4 (Box 100)
  - National Endowment for the Arts dance, 1977-1979; 3 (Box 100)
  - Boston Ballet, 1984-1994; 8 (Box 100)
  - Twin Theatre corporate records, undated (Box 100)
  - Sans Souci Theatre corporate records, undated (Box 100)
- February 1996 Acquisition, 1964; Series III; 0.21; (1 box)
  This acquisition consists of photographs and negatives.
  - 7 (copy) photographs of Bob Rauschenberg at the TEP (theater) in Paris, 2 (copy) photographs of Ben Lloyd, with negatives., 1964 (Box 101)